[
  {
    "question": "In \"Harry Potter and the Goblet of Fire,\" who is revealed to be the true identity of Mad-Eye Moody?",
    "choice1": "Barty Crouch Jr.",
    "choice2": "Sirius Black",
    "choice3": "Peter Pettigrew",
    "choice4": "Draco Malfoy",
    "answer": 1
  },
  {
    "question": "In \"Harry Potter and the Prisoner of Azkaban,\" what magical device does Hermione use to attend multiple classes simultaneously?",
    "choice1": "Time-Turner",
    "choice2": "Invisibility Cloak",
    "choice3": "Sneakoscope",
    "choice4": "Portkey",
    "answer": 1
  },
  {
    "question": "Which of the following Hogwarts houses values traits such as bravery, courage, chivalry, and daring?",
    "choice1": "Ravenclaw",
    "choice2": "Hufflepuff",
    "choice3": "Gryffindor",
    "choice4": "Slytherin",
    "answer": 3
  },
  {
    "question": "Which magical creature is known for its ability to transform into a person's worst fear?",
    "choice1": "Acromantula",
    "choice2": "Dementor",
    "choice3": "Thestral",
    "choice4": "Boggart",
    "answer": 4
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the primary ingredient in Polyjuice Potion that allows the drinker to temporarily assume the physical appearance of someone else?",
    "choice1": "Boomslang skin",
    "choice2": "Mandrake root",
    "choice3": "Lacewing flies",
    "choice4": "Bicorn horn",
    "answer": 1
  },
  {
    "question": "In \"Harry Potter and the Half-Blood Prince,\" what is the significance of the locket that Dumbledore and Harry retrieve from the cave?",
    "choice1": "It is the Philosopher's Stone",
    "choice2": "It contains the Resurrection Stone",
    "choice3": "It is a Portkey",
    "choice4": "It contains a Horcrux",
    "answer": 4
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the name of the mysterious and magical object that becomes the central focus of the trio's quest to defeat Voldemort?",
    "choice1": "The Resurrection Stone",
    "choice2": "The Elder Wand",
    "choice3": "The Philosopher's Stone",
    "choice4": "The Deathly Hallows",
    "answer": 4
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the significance of the \"Mirror of Erised\" and what does it show to those who look into it?",
    "choice1": "It shows the future, revealing the destiny of the person",
    "choice2": "It reflects the deepest desires of the heart",
    "choice3": "It reveals hidden truths about the person's past",
    "choice4": "It shows a distorted version of reality",
    "answer": 2
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the prophecy concerning Harry and Voldemort that is revealed in the Department of Mysteries?",
    "choice1": "Neither can live while the other survives",
    "choice2": "They are destined to be eternal enemies",
    "choice3": "They are long-lost brothers",
    "choice4": "Harry is the true heir of Slytherin",
    "answer": 1
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the Unforgivable Curse that causes intense pain to the victim without causing any physical harm?",
    "choice1": "Avada Kedavra",
    "choice2": "Imperius Curse",
    "choice3": "Cruciatus Curse",
    "choice4": "Sectumsempra",
    "answer": 3
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the name of the magical object that Dumbledore uses to retrieve and view memories?",
    "choice1": "Pensieve",
    "choice2": "Deluminator",
    "choice3": "Remembrall",
    "choice4": "Time-Turner",
    "answer": 1
  },
  {
    "question": "In \"Harry Potter and the Order of the Phoenix,\" what is the prophecy that is revealed in the Hall of Prophecy at the Department of Mysteries?",
    "choice1": "The one with the power to vanquish the Dark Lord approaches...",
    "choice2": "The chosen one will defeat Voldemort using the Elder Wand...",
    "choice3": "The Ministry of Magic will fall unless Voldemort is defeated...",
    "choice4": "The true heir of Slytherin will rise to power...",
    "answer": 1
  },
  {
    "question": "The real identity of the Half-Blood Prince?",
    "choice1": "Horace Slughorn",
    "choice2": "Tom Riddle",
    "choice3": "Remus Lupin",
    "choice4": "Severus Snape",
    "answer": 4
  },
  {
    "question": "Who is named Minister of Magic after the Battle of Hogwarts?",
    "choice1": "Rufus Scrimgeour",
    "choice2": "Cornelius Fudge ",
    "choice3": "Hermione Granger",
    "choice4": "Kingsley Shaklebolt",
    "answer": 4
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the name of the magical creature that Hagrid introduces to the Care of Magical Creatures class in \"Harry Potter and the Prisoner of Azkaban?\"",
    "choice1": "Acromantula",
    "choice2": "Hippogriff",
    "choice3": "Thestral",
    "choice4": "Blast-Ended Skrewt",
    "answer": 4
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the name of the spell used to summon objects to the caster's location?",
    "choice1": "Accio",
    "choice2": "Expelliarmus",
    "choice3": "Protego",
    "choice4": "Stupefy",
    "answer": 1
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the incantation for openning the Marauder's Map?",
    "choice1": "Mischief managed",
    "choice2": "Lumos",
    "choice3": "I solemnly swear that I am up to no good",
    "choice4": "Expecto Patronum",
    "answer": 3
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the name of the village near Hogwarts where students often visit to buy supplies and enjoy some leisure time?",
    "choice1": "Godric's Hollow",
    "choice2": "Hogsmeade",
    "choice3": "Diagon Alley",
    "choice4": "Ottery St. Catchpole",
    "answer": 2
  },
  {
    "question": "'Take a bath, and - er - take the egg with you, and - er - just mull things over in the hot water. It'll help you think... trust me.'",
    "choice1": "Nymphadora Tonks",
    "choice2": "Hannah Abbott",
    "choice3": "Justin Finch-Fletchley",
    "choice4": "Cedric Diggory",
    "answer": 4
  },
  {
    "question": "'Silly girl ... But Madam Pomfrey fixed her nose back on in the end.'",
    "choice1": "The Fat Friar",
    "choice2": "Nymphadora Tonks",
    "choice3": "Pomona Sprout",
    "choice4": "Justin Finch-Fletchley",
    "answer": 3
  },
  {
    "question": "'Oh, please... I don't think Expelliarmus is exactly going to help us against You-Know-Who, do you?'",
    "choice1": "Zacharias Smith",
    "choice2": "Hannah Abbott",
    "choice3": "Nymphadora Tonks",
    "choice4": "Cedric Diggory",
    "answer": 1
  },
  {
    "question": "'My dad's Muggle-born and he's a right old slob. I suppose it varies, just as it does with wizards?'",
    "choice1": "Nymphadora Tonks",
    "choice2": "Susan Bones",
    "choice3": "Cedric Diggory",
    "choice4": "Newt Scamander",
    "answer": 1
  },
  {
    "question": "'So - is it really true? You make a stag Patronus?'",
    "choice1": "Pomona Sprout",
    "choice2": "Susan Bones",
    "choice3": "Hannah Abbott",
    "choice4": "Nymphadora Tonks",
    "answer": 2
  },
  {
    "question": "'My philosophy is that worrying means you suffer twice.'",
    "choice1": "Nymphadora Tonks",
    "choice2": "Newt Scamander",
    "choice3": "Pomona Sprout",
    "choice4": "The Fat Friar",
    "answer": 2
  }
]